# Anugrah Wardhani

### **Software Developer**

West Bandung, Indonesia ardhanwardhani@gmail.com

https://ardhanwardhani.github.io (+62) 8584 6200 429

### **Summary**

A graduate of a vocational high school majoring in software engineering with an average score of 79. Has internship experience as a web developer for 6 months and a store crew for 3 years. Have a willingness to learn new things, attention to detail, good communication and leadership

# **Experience**

### Store Junior Leader at Indomaret

Feb 2022 - Aug 2022 (7 months)

- Maintain the appearance of the store in accordance with predetermined standards and SOPs.
- Product management to reduce damaged goods, both products on display or in warehouses.
- Ensure that each shift goes well according to the directions and targets that have been set.
- Take part in teamwork to achieve KPIs and achieve the best store performance

#### Store Crew Boy at Indomaret

Jul 2019 - Jan 2022 (2 years 7 months)

- Ensuring the cleanliness and tidiness of the store as a form of indirect service to consumers.
- Work with the team to keep the store clean and tidy for the smooth running of joint activities
- Manage products on display racks and warehouses to conform to the planogram and apply FEFO and FIFO principles

#### Web Developer Intern at CV. NineOD

Nov 2018 - Jan 2019 (3 months)

- · Learn the Ruby programming language and the Ruby on Rails framework.
- Understand the OOP paradigm and the concept of MVC
- · Create simple web-based programs: Discussion Forum

### Web Developer Intern at PT. Mediantara Kreasindo

Aug 2018 - Oct 2018 (3 months)

- · Learn and implement OOP and MVC paradigms
- Studying the Codelgniter framework and several libraries
- Create simple web-based programs : Extraculicular Member Management

#### **Education**

#### **SMKN 4 Padalarang**

High School Student, Software Engineering

2015 - 2018

- Basic Logic
- Programming (Web & Desktop)
- SQL & DBMS
- Basic IT Network

#### **Licenses & Certifications**

#### **Software Development Digital Bootcamp**

Padepokan 79 at Jun 2023

#### **Social Media Management Intensive Bootcamp**

TempatBelajar at Sep 2022

#### **Skills**

Software Development: HTML, CSS, PHP, Java, MySQL, Bootstrap, CodeIgniter, Laravel, Object Oriented Programming, SOLID Principle • Others: Detail & Goal Oriented, Leadership, Communication, Interpersonal, Time Management, Critical Thinking.

# **Project**

#### **Personal Website**

https://ardhanwardhani.github.io/ • May 2023 - Jul 2023 (3 months)

• Tools: HTML and CSS

#### **E-Gawe**

https://github.com/ardhanwardhani/egawe • Feb 2023 - Jul 2023 (6 months) Contact Management Web-based App

• Tools: CodeIgniter4, MySQL, Stisla Template

#### **Interests**

Self-Development: Growth Mindset, Communication Skill • Bussiness: Marketing, Content Creation.

## Languages

Bahasa (Native Speaker), English (Pasif - Basic)